s60blog.com 2012-03-21

# Privacy Policy | The S60 Blog

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy of “www.s60blog.com” has been posted and is effective as of June 04, 2008.

At The S60 Blog your privacy is important and we are committed to protecting your personal data. As used in this Privacy Policy (this “Policy”), the term “personal data” means data such as: your name, mailing address, e-mail address, internet service provider, telephone number, or other personal information that may be supplied by you or collected about you according to applicable local legislation. We hope that this Policy helps you understand what kind of personal data, if any, we collect at this site and how we handle and use any such personal data after collection.

**Applicability**

By accessing and using this site, your use indicates your agreement with the terms of this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use this site.

This Policy is applicable to this and certain other The S60 Blog general informational web/mobile sites, but not necessarily all The S60 Blog web/mobile sites or web channels, for which special terms and conditions may apply as indicated. All The S60 Blog sites to which this Policy is applicable are collectively referred to as this “site”. Note that special use terms, or site or page specific terms (referred to as “special terms”), may apply to certain pages/services on this site, but the applicability of any such special terms will be expressly indicated. In the event of any inconsistency between any special terms and this Policy, the applicable special terms will prevail over the terms of this Policy.

**Anonymous Use**

In general, most of this site’s pages are provided for informational purposes and you will be able to use this site without telling The S60 Blog who you are or providing The S60 Blog with any personal data about yourself. There are times, however, when in connection with your use of this site The S60 Blog may need information about you.

**Advertising**

We accept [advertisers](http://s60blog.com/advertise/) and at the same time use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Personal Data Provided by You**

To respond to your questions, fulfill your requests or manage interactive customer programs, it may be necessary to ask for or obtain personal data. If you provide us with any personal data, we may use it to respond to your requests, customize your user experience with us, determine your satisfaction with The S60 Blog products and/or services or contact you via mail, e-mail, mobile message or phone, or, in accordance with local law, contact you via the aforementioned channels to inform you of new products, services or promotions we may offer. By providing information to The S60 Blog through this site, you acknowledge and consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifying information of the type and for the limited purposes described in this Policy.

You expressly accept and give your consent that your personal data obtained in connection with your use of this site may be transferred, if permitted by applicable local legislation, across international borders to server locations supporting this site (including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your location) for operating and developing this site and The S60 Blog services, including transfers to The S60 Blog subcontractors or agents, as mentioned below, who perform tasks related to this site, or The S60 Blog services, or for the purposes of storing the data in relevant databases, which may be located in Finland or in any other country where The S60 Blog has operations.

If you place an order for a product, request a service or submit content to this site, we may need to contact you for additional information required to process or fulfill your order and/or request. Unless compelled by applicable law or administrative or judicial order, we will not provide this information to a third party without your permission, except as necessary to process your order, fulfill your requests, manage interactive customer programs or, if you are a corporate user, enable administration of access and usage of this site by authorized personnel in your organization. If allowed by applicable local legislation, The S60 Blog may also exchange information between The S60 Blog’s affiliated (related) companies for the purposes mentioned in this Policy.

Because The S60 Blog is committed to protecting your privacy, The S60 Blog does not engage in the practice of selling or trading personal data to other companies for promotional purposes.

**Usage of Subcontractors**

We may use subcontractors to provide some products or services to you. We also may need to share your personal data with these subcontractors so that they can provide services to us. Our subcontractors are not permitted to use such personal data for any other purposes and we impose confidentiality requirements on their services.

**Visitor Identification – Usage of “Cookies”**

From time to time, information may be placed on your computer to improve this site and The S60 Blog’s services for you. This information is commonly referred to as a “cookie”, which many web sites use. Cookies are pieces of data stored on your computer’s hard drive or browser, and not on this site. They typically enable collection of certain information about your computer, including your internet protocol address, your computer’s operating system, your browser type and the address of any referring sites.

The use of cookies provides benefits to you, such as eliminating the need for you to enter your password frequently during a session, or, where applicable, re-enter items you place in a shopping cart from visit to visit if you do not finish a transaction on an earlier visit. By showing how and when our visitors use this site or other The S60 Blog sites, the use of cookies allows The S60 Blog to continue to improve the sites. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits. Please understand that if cookies are turned off, you may not be able to view certain parts of this site that may enhance your visit. Some of our business partners whose content is linked to or from this site may also use cookies. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. This site also makes use of cookies for website traffic analysis and anonymous demographic profiling.

**Security**

The S60 Blog has endeavored to take commercially reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized access to and improper use of your personal data submitted to The S60 Blog via your use of this site. For example, The S60 Blog uses encryption technology when collecting financial personal data such as credit card information. If this site supports on-line transactions, it will use an industry standard security measure, such as the one available through “Secure Sockets Layer” (“SSL”), to protect the confidentiality and security of online transactions. If used, industry standard security measures like SSL authentication ensure that credit card information, as well as other personal data submitted as part of the buying process, is reasonably safe from third party interception.

While there are always risks associated with providing personal data, whether in person, by phone or via the internet or other technologies, and no system of technology is completely safe or “tamper”/”hacker” proof, The S60 Blog has endeavored to take reasonable precautions which are appropriate to the nature of the information to prevent and minimize such risks in connection with your use of this site.

**Accuracy of Collected Data**

The S60 Blog will on its own initiative, or at your request, free of charge, replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data retained by The S60 Blog in connection with the operation of this site. Please consult the contact us page on this site to determine how best to contact The S60 Blog to update and/or review your personal data and/or opt out of receiving marketing communications from The S60 Blog.  
**  
Minors**

The S60 Blog’s policy is to request that “Minors” (the age of Minors is determined by local law where you reside) do not make purchases or engage in other legal acts on this site without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, unless permitted by applicable local law.

**External Links**

This site may contain links to other sites. Please note that The S60 Blog is not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of any other sites. We recommend that you read the privacy policies of such sites.

**Changes to this Policy**

The S60 Blog may from time to time change this Policy or change, modify or withdraw access to this site at any time with or without notice. However, if this Policy is changed in a material, adverse way, The S60 Blog will post a notice advising of such change at the beginning of this Policy and on this site’s home page for 30 days. We recommend that you re-visit this Policy from time to time to learn of any such changes to this Policy.

2009 © The S60 Blog | All rights reserved.

{ Comments are closed. }
